

0

+38979333220



tomedimovski@hotmail.com



Bitola, 7000

#### LINKS

#### Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/tome.d imovski.3

#### **SKILLS**

Mobile device and computer management

Maintain equipment

Provide customer follow-up services

Good communication skills

Willingness to learn and develop

Diagnostics

Operating systems software

Technical support

Problem-solving and decision-making

Consulting and advising

Developing objectives and strategies

Working well in a team

Self-management

Organizational skills

Enthusiasm

Task prioritization

Discipline

Determination

Dedication

## LANGUAGES

English

Russian

# HOBBIES

Cycling, Technology, Travel, Movies...

# **Tome Dimovski**

### SENIOR CELL PHONE REPAIR TECHNICIAN

#### **ABOUT ME**

A solution-oriented, highly analytical, and resourceful candidate with over eight years of technical troubleshooting, end-user service, and network development experience. I have continuously demonstrated skills in the development and implementation of technological solutions with a special emphasis on delivering cost-cutting and productivity improvements. I am a professional in hardware and software configuration, testing as well as the repair of various hardware and software applications. I have a proven ability to provide creative and effective issue resolution through the application of highly developed problem-solving skills. I embody the right qualities of being a team player with a reputation for providing excellent user service and the tenacity to work with demanding clientele.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Cell Phone Repair Technician Telefonservis, Blvd. 1st May 134/3, Bitola, +38976227080 / Bitola / Mar 2017 - Present

Making cosmetic repairs, check and diagnose faults, perform flashing of handsets and function test, change batteries/accessories and liaise between other senior technicians, computer literate and adaptable to change within this role.

Main Duties & Responsibilities:

- Practicing Electro Static Discharge awareness in order to prevent accidental damage to equipment
- Performing basic fault finding
- Eliminating blacklisting, SIM card or network problems to ensure fault lies with the handset, or accessories
- Performing functionality checks in order to eliminate user error
- Performing functionality checks in order to eliminate user error
  Ascertain the warranty status of a handset in order to eliminate damaged equipment
- Performing functional test of handset using RF test equipment and PC in order to ascertain the nature of the defect/s (where applicable)
- Performing software related/cosmetic repair to handsets in order to remedy diagnosed fault
- Entering job details via TIM in order to maintain repairs database
- Repairing to manufacturers guidelines
- Supporting the team as and when necessary
- Achieving agreed targets as specified in order to meet the requirements of the business
- Maintaining equipment including anti static checks, regular calibration and the installation of software upgrades
- Using own initiative to improve performance and quality of line

# Computer Repair Technician Self-Employment / Bitola / Jan 2011 - Present

Responsibilities:

- Diagnosed and repaired hardware problems, troubleshoot technical problems, completely built computers, and installed software applications.
- Delivered, set up, and networked large computer systems on Windows OS
- Conceptualized, designed, oversaw the implementation of both wired and wireless networks with firewall and router configurations and anti-malware solutions.
- Customized personal computers to better serve customer needs.

## Warehouseman

# Vero Supermarket / Bitola / Jul 2012 - Apr 2013

Duties and responsibilities:

Varied daily tasks such as restocking shelves, accepting incoming orders, processing and packing orders, counting inventory, and ensuring orders are shipped in a timely manner.

# Gas Station Attendant

MakOil Gas Station - Bitola / Bitola / Oct 2007 - Aug 2009

High level of customer service skills. Provided and rendered prompt, efficient, and courteous service to customers. Received cash and gave correct change and processed credit card sales correctly through the terminal. Assisted and helped with inventory, stocking shelves, and monitoring inventory.

# EDUCATION

# High school diploma Technical High School Gjorgji Naumov / Bitola / 2000

Degree in mechanical engineering technology